inbedwithsue.com 2018-05-14

# 

**COLLECTING AND USING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

As you visit, browse, access or otherwise use the Company’s Website or Service or communicate with the Company, you may be asked to disclose certain Personal Information so that the Company can make you aware of the Website and provide you with access to the Service. So that you can reasonably determine whether to disclose your Personal Information to Company via the Website, or Service, the Company is providing you with these guidelines about how the Company collects uses and stores Personal Information. By visiting, accessing, browsing or using the Website, and in some cases becoming Members, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Online Privacy Policy. This Online Privacy Policy only applies to Personal Information collected on the Website and does not apply to information collected by the Company from you through any other means or to any third party link accessible through the Website. The Online Privacy Policy covers how the Company collects uses stores and shares Personal Information submitted and collected online as of the date upon which this Online Privacy Policy is posted (or as may be amended from time to time and posted on the Website). The Company may change this Online Privacy Policy at any time, for any reason. Any such changes, revisions, alterations or deletions made to this Online Privacy Policy shall become effective immediately upon posting. It is therefore important for you to visit this Online Privacy Policy from time to time. 

**IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY DO NOT ACCESS THE COMPANY’S WEBSITE OR USE ITS SERVICE.**

All defined terms set forth in the Company’s Terms of Use and Monthly Subscription Agreement posted on the Company’s Website shall have the same meaning in this Online Privacy Policy.. The following additional definitions shall apply governing this Privacy Policy. 

**“Personal Information,”** for purposes of this Privacy Policy shall mean data that is unique to an individual, such as a name, address, credit card or debit card number, e-mail address, postal or billing address and telephone number, whether contained in text or electronic messages, or mobile applications downloaded from our Website (if applicable) and providing dedicated non-browser based communications between the Company and you. 

**“Non-personal Identifiable Information”** shall mean any and all information, other than Personal Information, that does not identify a specific individual. Non-personal Identifiable Information may include your equipment, device, operating system or browser used to visit, access, browse or use the Website or Service; a your visiting or browsing or accessing or using activity or actions; summary information respecting our entire user base that may be collected by Company or its third party servers, including information about ads, sponsorships, products, goods or services provided through Third Party Links presented and clicked upon by you; any other information which provides Company with anonymous usage data (including, but not limited to, the number of unique visits, pages visited or navigational preferences); web browser information for facilitating communications between you and Company (including your MAC or IP address); “Cookies” or “Flash Cookies” or “Clear Gifts” technology allowing the Company to track repeat users and user’s usage patterns; Client-side page tagging or Pixel or Beacons tagging activities that allow the Company to make servicing users more efficient, and; content in any form or medium voluntarily submitted to the Company for posting and critique by Company representatives or users. The Company may provide, sell or transfer Non-personal Identifiable Information about user sales, traffic patterns, preferences or any other related Website or Service information to third parties. 

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

The Company only collects Personal Information voluntarily given to us by you. The Company does not require Visitors to provide it with any Personal Information to access public areas of our website; however, the Company may use or collect a Visitor’s IP Address and other diagnostic information to: a) diagnose problems with the Company’s server or Website or b) to identify you during your registration as a Member. If, however, you elect to register and qualify as and Member to order the Company’s Monthly Subscription Service, the Company will require that you access certain secure areas of the Website as well as provide the Company with Personal Information (including a Payment Source). Subject to the further conditions contained herein, 

The Company may use Personal Information for the following purposes: 

a) Verifying a Member’s identity so that we can be sure that all of communications are secure and confidential; 

b) Responding to inquiries or requests from a Member; 

c) Delivering the Service to a Member in the most efficient manner; 

d) Carrying out the Company’s and any Member’s obligations arising out of the Terms of Use or the Monthly Subscription Agreement, including transmitting your Personal Information to the relevant debit or credit card company for processing; 

e) Providing a Member with specific information requested by a Member, the request for which information constitutes Member’s consent to be contacted; 

f) Allowing a Member to voluntarily submit or critique Member Content, subject to the Company’s Terms of Use provisions on Member Content otherwise posted on the Website; and 

g) Notifying a Member, if required under the Terms of Use or the Monthly Subscription Agreement, of any changes to the Service or Terms of Use or the Monthly Subscription Service Agreement. 

A Member may update Member Personal Information that a Member provides the Company by logging on to “My Account” in accordance with the instructions posted on the Website. A Member may also request deletion or correction of its Personal Information or privacy preferences by emailing us at [support@suebryce.com](mailto:support@suebryce.com). 

Subject to the further terms hereof, the Company will not sell, license or otherwise transfer any rights to Personal Information to any third party unless a) expressly authorized by you; or b) such license, sale or other transfer is in connection with the sale, transfer, merger, reorganization, consolidation or other transaction involving all or part of the Company. 

Notwithstanding the foregoing, the Company will or may transmit or disclose Personal Information to third parties in the following circumstances: 

  * a)The Company uses certain third party contractors or vendors to perform certain services for us, including, but not limited to, webhosting, website maintenance and performance improvement tasks. In addition, should you register or attempt to register as a Member to order the Company’s Monthly Subscription Service (and, if once authorized as a Member to maintain your status as a validly registered Member) we must release your credit or debit card information or other Personal Information to a card-issuing bank to confirm payment for the service. The Company will also provide your email address information or other Personal Information to third parties under contract to us such that we can deliver the Monthly Subscription Service to a Member or receive and post Member Content on the Website. When any user or visitor subscribes to an Internet Service Provider (ISP) the computing device is assigned an IP Address, which the Company will track and store to manage security and monitor usage volume and patterns. 
  *   * b)The Company will disclose Personal Information: 1) if it is required to do so law or regulation or judicial order; 2) if we receive a validly issued subpoena issued by a court of competent jurisdiction; 3) to defend or enforce the Company’s rights under any Agreement between a User and the Company, including but not limited to this Online Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use relating to this Website or the Pay Subscription Service Agreement; or 4) if a you consent to the disclosure. 

**NOTICE TO EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA (EEA) MEMBERS**

**Personal information and Non-Personal Identifiable Information may be collected, transferred or stored at a destination outside the EEA. Such information may be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who may work for either Company directly or contractors retained by the Company to process such information, fulfill any order for Service, process payment or billing as well as support services. By submitting any information, an EEA user agrees to this collection, storing and transferring of information. Company agrees to take all reasonable steps to ensure your data is treated securely in accordance with this Online Privacy Policy.**

**NOTICE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS**

**California law gives California residents providing Personal Information to the Company the right to request once per calendar year that the Company provide users with information about how the Company has shared the user’s Personal Information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To the extent applicable, if at all, such information includes: a) list and names and addresses of all third parties with whom such Personal Information was shared during the prior calendar year along with a list of the categories of Personal Information shared. To make such a request, please send an email to**[ **support@suebryce.com**](mailto:support@suebryce.com) **and specifically reference “California Privacy Request” in the subject matter line. Your request should include your name, physical address (other than email address) and an email address. The Company will respond you your request within thirty (30) days of the receipt of your request.**

**The Company does not share Personal Information with third parties for their marketing purposes and will not do so without prior written consent.**

**CALIFORNIA “DO NOT TRACK” SETTINGS**

**Some web browsers have settings that allow users to request that Websites not track a user’s movement within a Website. The Company’s Website DOES NOT obey any such settings when transmitted to, or received (whether detected or not) by the Company’s Website.**

**Account Cancellation; Deletion of Personal Information**

Members desiring to cancel our terminate the Service may do so by logging on to its account, proceeding to the “My Account” section for billing and following the prompts for termination. The Company will store Personal Information as long as is necessary to provide you with the Monthly Subscription Service or until Company receives a termination notice pursuant to the immediately preceding procedure under the “My Account” section, provided however, that Company will continue to retain Personal Information after such Member’s termination as long as necessary to enforce our rights under the Terms of Use, the Monthly Subscription Agreement or this Privacy Policy. 

**Security**

We have adopted and adhere to stringent security standards designed to protect non-public Personal Information obtained or stored by the Company is protected from and against accidental or unauthorized access or disclosure. Among the safeguards that the Company has developed for this Website are administrative, physical and technical barriers that together protect the Website from unauthorized access or use. We may from time to time be required to shutdown the entire Website for security maintenance. 

The Company uses secure servers for all User information. Members accessing the Company Service must use [an SSL-enabled browser] in order to protect the confidentiality of any Personal Information. Members will be required to create and access an account by means of a unique User ID and Password. The Company will encrypt this Password. Members must abide by the Password and User ID requirements set forth in the Terms of Use and the Pay Subscription Content Service Agreement at all times. 

Notwithstanding the foregoing, users and Members acknowledge that no 100% guarantee can be made regarding the security of any data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network. Users accordingly acknowledge that: 1) there are security and privacy limitations respecting data transmissions over the Internet and in wireless networks; 2) the Company shall have no liability to any user, Member or third party for any loss, disclosure, alteration, modification or misuse of an information transmitted via the Internet or wirelessly; and 3) any information transmitted over the Internet or wirelessly may be subject to viewing or being tampered with by an unauthorized third party.
